Guide to the Bruce J. Zobel Papers, 1937-2008 MC 00259
Special Collections Research Center
- Education and Teaching, 1952-2001; MC 00259 Series 07; 16.0 Linear feet; 32 boxes
  The Education and Teaching series includes information about the courses Bruce Zobel taught, as well as the students he advised. The series begins with information about the many courses Zobel taught: semester courses, short courses, and courses at other institutions. Following the course information is restricted student information, then Ph.D. proposals, masters theses, and Ph.D. theses by Zobel's students.
  - Semester Courses, 1952-2001
    - Forestry 411: Forest Tree Genetics and Biology: Course Schedule, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Forestry 411: Forest Tree Genetics and Biology: Exams (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Forestry 411: Course Notes (Box 379, Folder 1)
    - Forestry 411: Forest Tree Genetics and Biology: Course Notes, 2001 (Box 379, Folder 2)
    - Forestry 411: Forest Tree Genetics and Biology: Problem Sets (Box 379, Folder 3)
    - Forestry 611: Forest Genetics: Course Notes, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Forestry 611: Forest Genetics (Box 379, Folder 5)
    - Forestry 441: Forest Tree Improvement: Course Schedules (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Forestry 611: Forest Genetics: Course Notes, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Forestry 441: Forest Tree Improvement: Problem Sets (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Forestry 611: Forest Genetics: Course Notes, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Forestry 441: Forest Tree Improvement: Exams (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Forestry 611: Forest Genetics: References, Problem Sets, Exams, Grade Reports (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Forestry 441: Forest Tree Improvement: Grade Reports (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Forestry 511: Tree Improvement Techniques: Course Schedule, Section I (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Forestry 511: Tree Improvement Techniques: Course Schedule, Section II (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Forestry 511: Tree Improvement Techniques: Course Schedule, Section III (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Forestry 511: Tree Improvement Techniques: Course Schedule, Section IV (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Forestry 511: Tree Improvement Techniques: Course Schedule, Section V (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Forestry 511: Tree Improvement Techniques: Course Schedule, Section VI-VII (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Forestry 511: Tree Improvement Techniques: Course Schedule, Section VIII (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Forestry 582: Silviculture and Management of Forest Plantations in the Tropics: Course Notes, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Forestry 582: Silviculture and Management of Forest Plantations in the Tropics: Course Notes, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      (Sessions 1-14)
    - Forestry 582: Silviculture and Management of Forest Plantations in the Tropics: Course Notes, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      (Sessions 15-27)
    - Forestry 582: Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 379, Folder 6)
    - Forestry 582: Silviculture and Management of Forest Plantations in the Tropics: Course Notes, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Forestry 582: Silviculture and Management of Forest Plantations in the Tropics: Exams (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Forestry 582: Silviculture and Management of Forest Plantations in the Tropics: Grade Reports (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Forestry 591: Tree Improvement Techniques: Course Schedule, Grade Reports, and Exams (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Forestry 782: Silviculture and Management of Forest Plantation in the Tropics: Course Notes, 2001 (Box 379, Folder 7)
    - Genetics 641: Colloquium in Speciation; Course Outline, Primary References, Lectures and Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 379, Folder 8)
    - Genetics 641: Colloquium in Speciation; Books-Introgressive Hybridization by Edgar Anderson, 1952, 1979 (Box 379, Folder 9)
    - Wood and Paper Science 413: Laboratory Instructions for Paper Properties and Additives, Department of Wood and Paper Science (Box 379, Folder 4)
    - General Course work: Handouts (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - General Course work: Handouts (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - General Course work: Handouts (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - General Course work: Handouts (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - General Course work: Handouts (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - General Course work: Handouts (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - General Course work: Handouts (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - General Course work: Handouts (Box 379, Folder 10)
    - General Course work: Miscellaneous Teaching Documents (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - General Course work: Retirement from Teaching, May, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Teaching Notes (Box 379, Folder 11)
  - Short Courses
    - North Carolina State University, 1958-2001
      - Forest Biology, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Genetics, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 1)
        Sessions 1-11
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 2)
        Sessions 12-15
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 3)
        Sessions 16-19
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 4)
        Sessions 20-25
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 5)
        Sessions 26-29
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 6)
        Sessions 30-31
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 7)
        Sessions 32-39
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 8)
        Sessions 40-43
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 9)
        Sessions 44-45
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 10)
        Sessions 46-48
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 11)
        Sessions 49-50
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 12)
        Sessions 51-52
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 1)
        Sessions 53-56
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 2)
        Sessions 57-58
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 3)
        Sessions 59-60
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 4)
        Sessions 61-62
      - Genetics, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 5)
        Sessions 63-68
      - Hardwood, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Hardwood, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Hardwood, 1976 (Box 379, Folder 12)
      - Hardwood, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Hardwood, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Hardwood, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 11)
        Sessions 1-5
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 12)
        Sessions 6-11
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 1)
        Sessions 16-18
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 2)
        Sessions 19-21
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 3)
        Sessions 22-25
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 5)
        Sessions 30-35
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 6)
        Sessions 36-40
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 7)
        Sessions 41-45
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 8)
        Sessions 46-50
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 9)
        Sessions 1-6
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 10)
        Sessions 7-16
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 11)
        Sessions 17-22
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 12)
        Sessions 23-29
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 1)
        Sessions 36-44
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 2)
        Sessions 45-46
      - Subtropical and Tropical Forestry, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 3)
        Sessions 47-48
      - Tree Improvement: Genetic Testing Manual (Box 379, Folder 13)
      - Tree Improvement, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Tree Improvement, January, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Tree Improvement, June, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Tree Improvement, June 30-July 25, 1969 (Box 379, Folder 14)
      - Tree Improvement, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Tree Improvement, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Tree Improvement, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Tree Improvement, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Tree Improvement, 1977 (Box 380, Folder 1)
      - Tree Improvement, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Tree Improvement, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 2)
        Introduction and Session 1
      - Tree Improvement, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 3)
        Sessions 2-10
      - Tree Improvement, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 4)
        Sessions 11-15
      - Tree Improvement, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 5)
        Sessions 16-20
      - Tree Improvement, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 6)
        Sessions 21-25
      - Tree Improvement, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Tree Improvement, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Tree Improvement, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 9)
        Sessions 32-40
      - Tree Improvement, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 10)
        Sessions 41-44
      - Tree Improvement, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Tree Improvement, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 12)
        Sessions 47-50
      - Tree Improvement, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 13)
        Sessions 51-55
      - Tree Improvement, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 1)
        Sessions 56-58
      - Tree Improvement, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Tree Improvement, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
        Sessions 61-63
      - Tree Improvement, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 4)
        Sessions 64-68
      - Tropical Tree Improvement and Genetics of Fast Growing Plantations in Latin America, 1980 (Box 380, Folder 2)
      - Tree Improvement, July 1981 (Box 380, Folder 3)
      - Tree Improvement, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Tree Improvement, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Tree Improvement, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 7)
        Sessions 7-9
      - Tree Improvement, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 8)
        Sessions 10-11
      - Tree Improvement, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Tree Improvement, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 10)
        Introduction
      - Tree Improvement, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 11)
        Sessions 1-10
      - Tree Improvement, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 12)
        Sessions 11-20
      - Tree Improvement, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 13)
        Sessions 21-35
      - Tree Improvement, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Tree Improvement, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 15)
        Sessions 41-47
      - Tree Improvement, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 1)
        Sessions 48-51
      - Tree Improvement, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 2)
        Sessions 1-3
      - Tree Improvement, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 3)
        Sessions 4-8
      - Tree Improvement, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 4)
        Sessions 9-19
      - Tree Improvement, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 5)
        Sessions 20-28
      - Tree Improvement, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 6)
        Sessions 29-35
      - Tree Improvement, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Tree Improvement, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 8)
        Sessions 7-17
      - Tree Improvement, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 9)
        Sessions 18-21
      - Tree Improvement, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 10)
        Sessions 22-23
      - Tree Improvement, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 11)
        Sessions 24-26
      - Tree Improvement, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 12)
        Sessions 27-29
      - Tree Improvement, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 13)
        Sessions 30-33
      - Tree Improvement, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Tree Improvement, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 1)
        Sessions 6-12
      - Tree Improvement, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 2)
        Sessions 13-18
      - Tree Improvement, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 3)
        Sessions 19-24
      - Tree Improvement, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 4)
        Sessions 25-28
      - Tree Improvement, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 5)
        Sessions 29-36
      - Tree Improvement, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 6)
        Sessions 37-42
      - Tree Improvement, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 7)
        Sessions 1-4
      - Tree Improvement, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 8)
        Sessions 5-10
      - Tree Improvement, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 9)
        Sessions 11-19
      - Tree Improvement, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 10)
        Sessions 20-26
      - Tree Improvement, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 11)
        Sessions 27-34
      - Tree Improvement, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 12)
        Sessions 35-36
      - Tree Improvement, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 13)
        Sessions 37-41
      - Tree Improvement, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Tree Improvement, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Tree Improvement, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 3)
        Sessions 6-10
      - Tree Improvement, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Tree Improvement, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Tree Improvement, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Tree Improvement, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 7)
        Sessions 26-30
      - Tree Improvement, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 8)
        Sessions 31-37
      - Tree Improvement, 2001 (Box 380, Folder 4)
    - TAPPI
      - Linear Programming, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 9)
        Atlanta, Georgia
      - Fast Grown Plantation Wood, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 10)
        Melbourne, Australia
      - University of Florida, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - University of Florida, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Texas Forest Service, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Other Institutions
      - Forest Resources Allocation, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 1)
        Mobile, Alabama
      - Forest Resources Allocation, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Forest Resources Allocation, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Forest Resources Allocation, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Forest Resources Allocation, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Forest Resources Allocation, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - CAMCORE, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 7)
        Venezuela, Sessions 1-4 (English)
      - CAMCORE, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 8)
        Venezuela, Sessions 5-10 (English)
      - CAMCORE, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 9)
        Venezuela, Sessions 11-17 (English)
      - CAMCORE, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 10)
        Venezuela, Sessions 18-22 (English)
      - CAMCORE, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 11)
        Venezuela, Sessions 1-4 (Spanish)
      - CAMCORE, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 12)
        Venezuela, Sessions 5-10 (Spanish)
      - CAMCORE, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 13)
        Venezuela, Sessions 11-17 (Spanish)
      - CAMCORE, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 14)
        Venezuela, Sessions 18-22 (Spanish)
  - Student Files
    These files are restricted. Consult Special Collections for more information.
    - Adams, Timothy (Box 39, Folder 1)
      Access is restricted. Please contact Special Collections Research Center for more information.
    - Adams, Wesley (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Balocchi, Claudio (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Balodis, Vilnis (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Barker, James (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Barrientos, Lillia (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Beineke, Walter (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Bellandi, Ricardo (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Bellinger, R. Daniel (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Bergman, Axel (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Blair, Roger (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Bolotin, Moshel (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Brouard, Jean (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Brown, Sheryl (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Busby, Cheryl (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Caballero, Miguel (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Cannon, Phillip (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Carson, Michael (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Castillo, Jaime (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Caulfield, Jon (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Cech, Frank (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Chang, Wei-Ming (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Chuntanaparb, Lert (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Cole, Donald (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Conkle, M. Thompson (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Corriveau, Armand (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Coulter, Edward (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Cretcher, Gary (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Deines, James (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Delmastro, Roberto (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Denison, Neville (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Dietrichson, Jon (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Donahue, Jeffrey (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Dvorak, William (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Emery, Bruce (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Endoe, Masatoshi (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Equiluz, Teobaldo (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Fernandes, Erick (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Franklin, Carlyle (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Gallegas, Carl (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Garlo, Albert (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Gladstone, William (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Goggans, James (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Gomide, Jose (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Goncalves, Paulo (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Gregory, Jimmy (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Haracharik, David (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Harbin, Michael (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Harding, Kevin (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Harritt, Margaret (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Hatakeyama, Sukichi (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Haught, Alden (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Henri, Carolyn (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Hodges, James (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Hubbard, Susan (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Hudson, Berman (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Hunter, Serena (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Ibrahim, Sheikh (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Jadjuabsien, Sacorn (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Jaramillo, Carlos (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Jasso, Jesus (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Jayawickrama, Keith (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - John, Sally (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, George (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Johnson, John (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Juardo-Blano, Juan (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Kanashiro, Milton (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Kane, Michael (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Kang, Hyun-Chung (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Kang, Ke-Won (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Kasile, Joseph (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Kellison, Robert (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Kelly, Charles (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Kinloch, Bohun (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Kitchen, Robert (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Kitzmiller, Jennings (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Kundt, John (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Lambeth, Clements (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Lamontagne, Yves (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Land, Samuel (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Lane, Carl (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Lantz, Clark (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Leach, Gregory (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Ledig, Fred (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Lee, J. Charles (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Lewis, Ralph (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Liegel, Leon (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Lima, Roy (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Long, Alan (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Lowerts, George (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Makoui, Kambiz (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Mallchee, Edward (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Matthews, Frederick (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Matziris, Dimitrios (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - McCall, Early (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - McCutchan, Barbara (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - McKeand, Steven (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - McElwee, Robert (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Mengle, Dennis (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Miller, Lawrence (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Moreschi, Joao (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Namkong, Gene (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Nickles, Donald (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Osorio, Luis (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Otegbeye, Gbadesigin (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Overtone, Ronald (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Owino, Frederick (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Paschke, Jeffrey (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Pederick, Leon (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Polk, Randolph (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Porterfield, James (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Porterfield, Richard (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Posey, Clayton (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Pousouja, Reungchai (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Principe, Eduardo (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Purnell, Robert (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Quijada, Marcelino (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Roberds, James (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Rockwood, Donald (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Rose, Robert (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Ross, Roseanne (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Salem, Mahmoud (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Saylor, Leroy (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Schmitt, Daniel (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Schoenhofen, Leo (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Schultz, Emily (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Shelbourne, Cyril (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Shimizu, Jarbas (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Slichter, Timothy (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Sluder, Earl (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Donald (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Henry (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Robert (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Sniezko, Richard (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Sombun, Kowit (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Sossaman, Edward (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - South, David (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Stahl, Per (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Steinhoff, Raphael (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Stonecypher, Roy (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Struve, Daniel (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Stubblefield, George (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Sumantakul, Vichien (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Taft, Kinglsey (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Talbert, John (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Tarras, Michael (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Taylor, Fred (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Thorbjornson, Eyvid (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Torrico, Martin (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Van Buijtenen, Johannes (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Van Wyck, Gert (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Varrell, Judson (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Veal, Michael (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Von Wedel, Kay (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Von Weissenberg, Kim (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Wearsteler, Kenneth (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Webb, Charles (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Weber, Joseph (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Webster, Steve (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Weir, Robert (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Welby, Mary (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Wesley, John (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - White, Timothy (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Whitesell, Craig (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Wilcox, Michael (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Williams, Claire (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Windham, Jerry (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Yahya, Mouffaq (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Students, Duke University (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Students, Australia (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Roster of Students Advised (Box 380, Folder 5)
  - Ph.D. Proposals
    - Barker, James A. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Beineke, Walter F. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Blair, Roger (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Brouard, J.S. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Buckner, Edward (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Busby, Cheryl (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Cannon, Philip (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Carson, M.J. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Caulfield, Jonathan (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Chuntanaparb, Lert (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Cole, Donald (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Corriveau, Armand (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Dvorak, William (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Eguiluz, Teobaldo (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Emery, Bruce (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Franklin, E.C. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Gallegos, Carl (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Gladtsone, William (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Groggins, James (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Haracharik, David (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Harding, Kevin (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Harritt, Margaret (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Henri, Caroline (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Hodge, Gary (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Hubbard, S.D. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Johnson, John W. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Kane, Michael (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Kang, Hyung-Chung (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Kang, Kewon (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Kasile, Joseph (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Kellison, Robert (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Kinloch, B.B. (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Kitzmiller, John (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Kundt, John (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Lambeth, Clem (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Land, Samuel (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Lantz, Clark (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Lee, J. Charles (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Lewis, Ralph (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Long, Alan (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Lowerts, George (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Mallonee, Edward (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Makoui, Kambiz (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Matziris, Dimitrios (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - McElwee, R.L. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - McKeand, Steven (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Namkong, Gene (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Nickles, D.G. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Overton, Ronald (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Owino, Fred (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Paschke, Jeffrey (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Posey, Clayton (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Pousujja, Reungchai (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Purnell, Robert (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Quijada, Marcelino (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Roberds, James (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Rockwood, Donald (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Schmidt, Daniel (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Schultz, Emily (Box 53, Folder 8)